question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 1988 film 'Akira', Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash's starting Pokemon in the pilot episode of the cartoon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films 'Wolf Children' "
                 "and 'The Boy and the Beast'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The anime 'Lucky Star' follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 'Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya"
                 "' series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pokemon, Ash's Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 'Toaru Kagaku no Railgun' anime,  espers can only reach a "
                 "maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack 'Kamehameha' in Dragon Ball Z was "
                 "named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
